pbmining.com 2014-11-30

# PBMining | Privacy Policy

* * *

PB Mining respects the privacy of its customers and visitors. If you have any questions about the operation of our website, please contact us. We will answer any questions you may have! 

Our website collects names, email addresses, and other personal information from customers and visitors only when submitted via our registration form. This data is used solely by PB Mining and is not shared, traded, or sold to third parties. 

Our website also collects non-personal data through the use of server-based "session variables" which we use to achieve important site functionality, including the recognition of logged in users. 

Our web server also records IP addresses from all visitors to our site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to adminster our site, to analyze trends, to track user movement, and to gather broad demographic information -- all for the purpose of continually improving our website and delivering personlized, custom content. IP addreses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and their collection is standard procedure in most web server environments. 

By using pbmining.com, you signify your agreement to our privacy policy as stated above. Note that this policy may be revised periodically without notice. Please re-read this policy prior to submitting any personal information or if you have concerns about how your information is being collected and used.
